storeyourboard.com 2012-12-14

# Privacypolicy

_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/details.html) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._

 _StoreYourBoard.com a SPIRE LLC Company Privacy Policy_

**Our Commitment To Your Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy the following notice explains the information we collect, how it is used, how it is safeguarded, and how to contact us if you have any concerns.

 **Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We collect the following personal information from you

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number

  * Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

We use this information to

  * Fulfill your order

  * Send you an order confirmation

  * Assess the needs of your business to determine suitable products

  * Send you requested product or service information

  * Send product updates or warranty information

  * Respond to customer service requests

  * Administer your account

  * Send you a newsletter

  * Send you marketing communications

  * Administer contests and sweepstakes you entered, and notify you if you won

  * Respond to your questions and concerns

  * Improve our Web site and marketing efforts

  * Conduct research and analysis

  * Facilitate your transactions with other users

 **Choice/Opt-Out**

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at [support@storeyourboard.com](mailto:support@storeyourboard.com)

 **Information Obtained from Third Parties**

If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.

 **Information Sharing**

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information **_only as necessary to provide_** these services to us.

We may also disclose your personal information

  * as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process

  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,

  * if StoreYourBoard is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, 

  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so. 

We make your contact information available to other users that you transact with on this site to help complete the transaction.

 ** _PayPal_**

If you choose to use PayPal to finalize and pay for your order, you will provide your credit card number, directly to PayPal. PayPal's privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on the PayPal Web site.

 ** _Yahoo! Merchant Solutions_**

This site is hosted by Yahoo! Merchant Solutions. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and collects your billing information directly from you for the purpose of processing that information on our behalf. If you accessed _www.StoreYourBoard.com_ through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience to allows us better understand who visits the site. Please see the [Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/details.html) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information.

Yahoo! Merchant Solutions uses cookies and log files to track visitors to our site. The statistics collected provide us information about Web site usage.

 **Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information.

We use another company to place cookies on your computer to collect non-personally identifiable information to compile aggregated statistics for us about visitors to our site.

 ** _Web beacons_**

Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.

Our Web pages may also contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) that are set by our third party partners. Web beacons are used along with cookies enabling our partners to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used.

We use a third party to gather information about how you and others use our Web site. For example, we will know how many users access a specific page and which links they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used.

 ** _Links to Other Web Sites_**

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of StoreYourBoard.com. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit. 

**Security**

When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at _[support@storeyourboard.com](mailto:support@storeyourboard.com)_

In order to make a purchase from us, you must use our shopping cart provider (Yahoo Merchant Services) to finalize and pay for your order. Its privacy statement and security practices will also apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy statement before providing your information.

 **Additional Policy Information**

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

 **Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information**

To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, contact us at _support@ storeyourboard.com_

 **Contact Information**

You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below:

StoreYourBoard.com

536 Pantops Center #361

Charlottesville VA 22911

Email: _support@storeyourboard.com_

Phone: 1-800-701-3743
